Mss.Rec.55 Mss.Rec.55
American Philosophical Society
Pima Bajo recordings
1965
Mss.Rec.55
American Philosophical Society
12.0 Reel(s)
Linguistic field recordings in the Pima Bajo language, primarily elicitations conducted in Spanish. Recorded in Yecora, Sonora, Mexico, in the summer of 1965.
12 sound tape reels (23 hr., 14 min.): analog, 3 3/4 ips, 2 track, mono; 5 in.
Duarte O., Leonardo
Dunnigan, Timothy
Related Archival Materials
Project report on fieldwork in the Highland dialect with very brief discussion concerning phonology and syntax available in the Phillips Fund Collection (Mss.497.3.Am4).
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Presented by Timothy Dunnigan in 1965. This material was recorded with the assistance of a Phillips Fund grant.
Indians of Mexico--Sonora (State); Pima Bajo language; Sound recordings
- Audio recordings
  - Pima Bajo elicitations, 1965-06; 01-01; 1.0 .mp3; 01:04:02; Duarte O., Leonardo; Dunnigan, Timothy
    Scope and Contents note
    Words, phrases, and sentences elicited in Spanish, given in Pima Bajo. Recorded at Yecora, Sonora, Mexico.
    Existence and Location of Originals note
    This file is a compressed, digitized version of the original. The APS Library maintains the original format (Sound tape reel) as well as an uncompressed digitized version of this recording.
    Indians of Mexico--Sonora (State); Pima Bajo language; Pima Bajo language--Grammar; Yecora (Sonora, Mexico)
  - Pima Bajo elicitations, 1965-06; 01-02; 1.0 .mp3; 00:57:16; Duarte O., Leonardo; Dunnigan, Timothy
  - Pima Bajo elicitations, 1965-06; 02-01; 1.0 .mp3; 01:04:01; Duarte O., Leonardo; Dunnigan, Timothy
    Words, phrases, and sentences given in Pima Bajo and Spanish. Recorded at Yecora, Sonora, Mexico.
  - Pima Bajo elicitations, 1965-06; 02-02; 1.0 .mp3; 00:57:16; Duarte O., Leonardo; Dunnigan, Timothy
  - Pima Bajo elicitations, 1965-06; 03-01; 1.0 .mp3; 01:03:57; Duarte O., Leonardo; Dunnigan, Timothy
  - Pima Bajo elicitations, 1965-06; 03-02; 1.0 .mp3; 00:57:18; Duarte O., Leonardo; Dunnigan, Timothy
  - Pima Bajo elicitations, 1965-06; 04-01; 1.0 .mp3; 01:04:11; Duarte O., Leonardo; Dunnigan, Timothy
  - Pima Bajo elicitations, 1965-06; 04-02; 1.0 .mp3; 00:57:37; Duarte O., Leonardo; Dunnigan, Timothy
    Words, phrases, and sentences given in Pima Bajo and Spanish. Recorded at Yecora, Sonora, Mexico. Ending cut-off.
  - Pima Bajo elicitations, 1965-06; 05-01; 1.0 .mp3; 01:04:28; Duarte O., Leonardo; Dunnigan, Timothy
  - Pima Bajo elicitations, 1965-06; 05-02; 1.0 .mp3; 00:56:50; Duarte O., Leonardo; Dunnigan, Timothy
  - Pima Bajo elicitations, 1965-06; 06-01; 1.0 .mp3; 01:04:46; Duarte O., Leonardo; Dunnigan, Timothy
  - Pima Bajo elicitations, 1965-06; 06-02; 1.0 .mp3; 00:56:54; Duarte O., Leonardo; Dunnigan, Timothy
  - Pima Bajo elicitations, 1965-07; 07-01; 1.0 .mp3; 01:04:16; Duarte O., Leonardo; Dunnigan, Timothy
  - Pima Bajo elicitations, 1965-07; 07-02; 1.0 .mp3; 00:57:16; Duarte O., Leonardo; Dunnigan, Timothy
  - Pima Bajo elicitations, 1965-07; 08-01; 1.0 .mp3; 01:05:04; Duarte O., Leonardo; Dunnigan, Timothy
  - Pima Bajo elicitations, 1965-07; 08-02; 1.0 .mp3; 00:56:29; Duarte O., Leonardo; Dunnigan, Timothy
  - Pima Bajo elicitations, 1965-07; 09-01; 1.0 .mp3; 01:33:33; Duarte O., Leonardo; Dunnigan, Timothy
  - Pima Bajo elicitations, 1965-07; 09-02; 1.0 .mp3; 00:57:40; Duarte O., Leonardo; Dunnigan, Timothy
  - Pima Bajo elicitations, 1965-07; 10-01; 1.0 .mp3; 01:04:02; Duarte O., Leonardo; Dunnigan, Timothy
  - Pima Bajo elicitations, 1965-07; 10-02; 1.0 .mp3; 00:57:28; Duarte O., Leonardo; Dunnigan, Timothy
  - Pima Bajo elicitations, 1965-07; 11-01; 1.0 .mp3; 01:04:47; Duarte O., Leonardo; Dunnigan, Timothy
  - Pima Bajo elicitations, 1965-07; 11-02; 1.0 .mp3; 00:56:43; Duarte O., Leonardo; Dunnigan, Timothy
  - Pima Bajo elicitations, 1965-07; 12-01; 1.0 .mp3; 00:57:44; Duarte O., Leonardo; Dunnigan, Timothy